<documentation>
  <summary>
    This document provides method-level documentation for the LINQ_Assignment project.
    The project consists of three core functionalities:
    - Retrieving even numbers from an array.
    - Shuffling an array and returning odd numbers.
    - Computing statistical metrics (average, min, max) for an array.
  </summary>

  <class name="GetEven">
    <summary>
      Provides functionality to retrieve even numbers from an integer array using LINQ.
    </summary>
    <method name="GetEvenNumbers">
      <summary>
        Returns all even numbers from an array with an option to skip items.
      </summary>
      <param name="numbers">An integer array representing the dataset.</param>
      <param name="skip">An optional parameter that skips a specified number of even numbers.</param>
      <returns>A collection of even numbers from the input array.</returns>
      <example>
        <![CDATA[
        int[] numbers = { 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 };
        var evens = GetEven.GetEvenNumbers(numbers, 2);
        // Result: { 6, 8 }
        ]]>
      </example>
    </method>
  </class>


  <class name="GetOdd">
    <summary>
      Provides functionality to shuffle an array and retrieve odd numbers using LINQ.
    </summary>
    <method name="GetShuffledOddNumbers">
      <summary>
        Shuffles an array and returns only the odd numbers.
      </summary>
      <param name="numbers">An integer array representing the dataset.</param>
      <param name="skip">An optional parameter that skips a specified number of odd numbers.</param>
      <returns>A shuffled collection of odd numbers from the input array.</returns>
      <example>
        <![CDATA[
        int[] numbers = { 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 };
        var odds = GetOdd.GetShuffledOddNumbers(numbers, 1);
        // Result (shuffled): { 5, 7, 1 }
        ]]>
      </example>
    </method>
  </class>

<class name="GetArray">
    <summary>
      Provides functionality to compute statistical measures from an integer array.
    </summary>
    <method name="GetStatistics">
      <summary>
        Computes and returns the average, minimum, and maximum of the provided array.
      </summary>
      <param name="numbers">An integer array representing the dataset.</param>
      <returns>A tuple containing (average, minimum, maximum) values.</returns>
      <example>
        <![CDATA[
        int[] numbers = { 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 };
        var stats = GetArray.GetStatistics(numbers);
        // Result: (3.0, 1, 5)
        ]]>
      </example>
    </method>
  </class>

  <notes>
    <bullet>The methods in this project utilize LINQ for efficient filtering and querying.</bullet>
    <bullet>Random shuffling in GetShuffledOddNumbers is achieved using System.Random.</bullet>
    <bullet>Unit tests have been implemented to validate all methods.</bullet>
    <bullet>XML documentation is provided to assist with IntelliSense and automated documentation generation.</bullet>
  </notes>
</documentation>